https://www.mecpl.com/legal/privacy-policy/

Submit
Visit Us
MENUMENUMEC Thermal SprayAbout Us
HistoryVision Policy and ValueApprovals and CertificationsOrganization ChartWarrantiesClients
Products
Coating Equipments
Arc Spray Coating System – ArcjetPlasma Thermal Spray CoatingsHVOF Thermal Spray CoatingsFlame Spray SystemsCold SprayLaser Cladding
Turnkey System ProjectsConsumables and Spares
Replacement SparesThermal Spray WiresThermal Spray PowdersMasking Tapes and Compounds
Surface Preparation Equipments
Standard Cabinet Type Blasting MachinesVacuum Blasting MachinesPortable Blasting machinesSpecial Blasting Machines
Shot Peening Machines
Aerospace IndustrySteam Turbine IndustryGas Turbine IndustryPetro Chemical Industry
Auxiliary EquipmentsPowder Feeder
Services
Job WorkThermal Spray Training ProgramConsultancyTesting and Calibration
Research
Thermal Spray Coating FacilitiesThermal Spray Testing FacilitiesRegistrations and PatentsThermal Spray Technical AssociationsThermal Spray Publications
Literature
Thermal Spray AdvertisementsDownloads
FAQ
TerminologyWhat is Thermal Spray ?
Legal
Standard Terms and Conditions of Sale and DeliveryPrivacy PolicyLegal Disclaimer
Careers
Why MECHiring ProcessHuman Resource – TrainingCorporate Social ResponsibilitiesCorporate Governance
Contacts
Reach UsEnquiry FormThermal Spray World Wide
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining it. When you shop via our Web site, we will ask you to input your information and will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone/ mobile number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and password.
We may also collect information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .com .au and .com), your browser type, where you located in the country, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on. We may collect this information even if you do not register with us. None of this data is of a personal nature and will help us improve the quality of our service.
We at Metallizing Equipment Co. Pvt. Ltd recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not furnish any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. The information you give to us is held with the utmost care and security. This information is collected primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver you a truly personalized shopping experience. When navigating our web site, personal information about you is not collected automatically or without your knowledge.
We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. We may share non-personal, non-individual statistical or demographic information in aggregate form with our marketing partners, advertisers or other third-parties for research and advertising purposes. In other words, we will not tell our marketing partners that you purchased a specific product, but we may tell them how many customers purchased that product.
Security of Information –
When you place an order on mecpl.com website for a product, we offer the use of a secure server. The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypts all the information you input before it is sent to us. This prevents your personal data from being interpreted even if hacked while submitting it to our server. At the time of submitting your Credit Card details you will be redirected to a Highly Secure Payment server where Metallizing Equipment Co. Pvt. Ltd and its associates have no access to your information. Metallizing Equipment Co. Pvt. Ltd always see to that your privacy is maintained at all time during your time of transaction through our web site. We will not disclose any sort of personally identifiable information except when you give us requisite permission or under special circumstances such as when the law requires it.
A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser which tracks your movements within websites. Our site uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, the contents of your shopping cart, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance.
In case if you feel that your personal information should be change then you can change those information by “SIGN IN” and update the profile. There, you will be allowed to change any of your personal information that you might have entered before with us. In case you have trouble changing your information, you may email us via TICKET, our customer care department will help you to do so.
In summary Metallizing Equipment Co. Pvt. Ltd always respect the privacy of our customers completely. We use the information we collect on the Store to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
E-101, MIA, 2nd Phase, Basni, Jodhpur, India
Call Back
+91-291-2747601
marketing@mecpl.com
trade@mecpl.com
sales@mecpl.com
©2007-2019, Metallizing Equipment Co. Pvt. Ltd. All Right Reserved.
MEC uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website Got it.
